exampundit.in 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy - Exampundit.in

Privacy Policy

Exampundit.in  
built the Exampundit app as an Ad Supported app. This SERVICE is provided by  
Exampundit.in at no cost and is intended for use as is.

This  
page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the  
collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to  
use our Service.

If  
you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of  
information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we  
collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or  
share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The  
terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and  
Conditions, which is accessible at Exampundit unless otherwise defined in this  
Privacy Policy.

**Information  
Collection and Use**

For  
a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us  
with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to  
Mobile Number, Email Address. The information that we request is will be  
retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.

The  
app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify  
you.

Link  
to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app

**Log  
Data**

We  
want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in  
the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your  
phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your  
device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version,  
the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of  
your use of the Service, and other statistics.

**Cookies**

Cookies  
are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique  
identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and  
are stored on your device internal memory.

This  
Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third  
party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collection information and to  
improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these  
cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse  
our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.

**Service  
Providers**

We  
may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

  * To  
facilitate our Service;
  * To  
provide the Service on our behalf;
  * To  
perform Service-related services; or
  * To  
assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

We  
want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to  
your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them  
on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the  
information for any other purpose.

**Security**

We  
value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are  
striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember  
that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic  
storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute  
security.

**Links  
to Other Sites**

This  
Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you  
will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated  
by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these  
websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content,  
privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

**Children’s  
Privacy**

These  
Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect  
personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we  
discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we  
immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and  
you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please  
contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.

**Changes  
to This Privacy Policy**

We  
may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to  
review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any  
changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are  
effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

**Contact  
Us**

If  
you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate  
to contact us at exampundit@gmail.com.

No votes so far! Be the first to rate this post. 

##  We are sorry that this post was not useful for you! 

Let us improve this post! 

Tell us how we can improve this post? 

Thanks for your feedback!
